on the indication of the pastor, the first bachelor church, Mr. Jerry Kendall.
Thank you for the honor to be here. Let's pray. God, I thank you so much for this town. I thank
you for our council members and all those who serve this city well. It's the father we pray that
your hand of blessing would continue to be on it. Father, as we see you moving about, would you
just continue to help us to to love our neighbor and to lift you up and everything that we do.
Father, would you give this council wisdom? Would you give them exactly what they need to continue to
lead our town in a way that would honor you and to bring you glory? Father, would you protect
our first responders and and just continue to watch over them? God, we thank you that we live in this
free nation and this wonderful town and God, it is such a blessing, but we thank you most of all
for your son, Jesus Christ, in his name we pray, amen. I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United
States of America and to the Republic for which it stands, one nation under God in the visible
with liberty and justice for all.
Oh, we're public input. Let's give the personal appearances. God, cleanse list.
I wish to approve.
Easter. Hi.
Six minutes from the September 2nd, 2025 regular meeting.
I wish to approve. Second.
I wish to approve.
Easter.
Aye. Seven.
They wish to remain claim from Pensacola, GRDA, Relicencing, and Associated Complaint,
proceedings that amount of $9,843 in 20 cents.
Yes, so this was doing what, like it said, the combined
proceedings plus also, you know, asking some questions along the way on our settlement that we went
through and everything like that. So we budgeted this year, 750,000. If this claim is approved,
then it will leave the remaining balance of $740,000, $36.80.
If both of those of this and the next item are approved,
they'll leave us $739,871 in 80 cents.
I'll make questions.
I approve. Second.
Jones, hi.
Four and five.
Easter.
Hi.
Global. Hi.
Harper.
Hi.
Hey, good day. I'll start in the end.
I'm in the Palmer Clinic for Pensacola, GRDA, Relicencing,
and Associated Complaint,
Proceedings, and amount of $165.
So this is just the same stuff, $165.
First, obviously with this settlement, going on, we should, this should slow down from this firm,
drastically so.
I'll make most of them approve.
Second.
Jones, hi.
Four and five.
Easter.
Hi.
Global.
Harper.
Hi.
Nine other new business, which has risen since the position of this agenda.
Ten staff reports.
Eleven, trustee, community, and athletes.
Twelve, trust manager, communication.
Yes, sir.
Thirteen agenda.
I'm going to speak with you later.
Easter.
Hi.
Global.
Jones.
Hi.
Four and five.
Harper.
Hi.